Erica Elaine Boyd 65 Cassandra Blvd Unit 206, West Hartford, CT 06107 617-678-8043 ♦ saviora@gmail.com

Quality Assurance Analyst with more than 5 years of experience in IT analysis, business analysis, quality assurance and editorial assistance. Frequent temporary assignments have resulted in the ability to learn new tasks quickly and easily adapt to change.

EDUCATION:

Bachelor of Arts and Sciences, Japanese Language and Literature Wellesley College, Class of 2006

.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:

Temporal Annotator (temporary position)

January 2012 to Present

SUNY, Albany, NY (via SUNY)

• Working remotely between 5 - 20 hours per week tagging and linking time and event references within hospital records in order to create a narrative timeline and improve the efficiency of database searches for patient histories.

Guest Recognition Coordinator (temporary position)

April 2011 to August 2011

Ritz – Carlton, Boston, MA (via Hollister Associates)

- Ensured that the amenities of the V.I.P. guests were assessed and delivered.
- Went above and beyond the call of duty to locate jasmine candles for the In-Room Dining Dept. as well as put together the May newsletter for the Residences in the manager's absence.

Editorial Assistant (temporary position)

August 2010 to September 2010

Nature Publishing, Cambridge, MA (via OfficeTeam)

- Brought on to ensure that the September deadline was met after staff was cut; assisted
 with the web editing and mobile application publishing of educational materials for
 Scitable.com.
- Tight deadline was met due to strong learning curve and willingness to work overtime.

Editorial Assistant (temporary position)

February 2010 to August 2010

Pearson, Inc., Boston, MA (via Leafstone Staffing)

- Assisted with the proofing and revising of the FL, GA, and National middle school (grades 6 & 7) textbooks for the Social Studies Curriculum department.
- Enabled the department to deliver ahead of schedule
- Remove flaws in the artwork and organization of the textbook page numbers and quiz topics that would have otherwise been overlooked.

Assistant Director of Student Care

September 2008 to January 2010

Lesley University, Cambridge, MA

- Reviewed and processed graduate applications for NH, ME, and central and western MA satellite program admissions.
- The admission process was made more expedient by the improved letters, emails, and other correspondence to students that I assisted in creating.

QA iBAAG Analyst (temporary position) United Health Group, Hartford, CT(via Aerotek)

September 2007 to January 2008

- Ensured the accuracy of customer benefits through proofing and fact-checking; also applied and audited state legislation.
- Instrumental in discovering and correcting inaccurate language that prevented same-sex couples from receiving the insurance coverage to which they were entitled.

Repricing Specialist (temporary position) Aetna, Windsor, CT (via Enherent)

April 2007 to September 2007

- Provided proper discounts on procedures based on the available provider contracts.
- Repriced PPO medical and dental bills while exceeding daily bill guota on a regular basis.

Eligibility QA Analyst (temporary position)

June 2005 to August 2005

- CIGNA Healthcare, Bloomfield, CT (via Kelly Services)
 - Aided in making CIGNA's eligibility policies compliant with HIPAA by providing assistance with implementing the appropriate changes to all member eligibility platforms.
 - Enabled managers and other testers to track changes in HIPAA compliant eligibility requirements and the resulting altered functions of their data and record systems.

COMPUTER SKILLS:

Proficient in:

- Microsoft® Office
- Mac OS
- Windows NT through 7
- Test Director
- Opera (database)
- Datatel
- Mystique
- Microsoft® Publisher
- Smart Review
- Mozilla Firefox
- Adobe Photoshop
- Microsoft® Entourage Opera (Browser

- Mozilla Thunderbird
- Microsoft® Outlook
- Adobe Reader
- Microsoft® Internet Explorer
- Lotus Notes
- 7 ZIP
- FTP
- Total Uninstall
- CSS
- ORBIT/CDX
- Ubuntu

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS:

- Web applications/content design
- Online/mobile publishing
- Writing/editing

- Quality assurance analysis
- Customer service
- Japanese language skills

REFERENCES:

Kyle Murphy, PhD

Assistant Editor Nature Publishing Group 25 First Street, Suite 104 Cambridge, MA 02141 USA Phone: 617.475.9209

Email:

k.murphy@us.nature.com

Michele Chaurette McKenna

Associate Director of Student Office of National Programs **Lesley University** 29 Everett Street Cambridge, MA 02138 Phone: 800-999-1959 x8569 Direct Phone: 617-349-8569

E-Mail:

mchauret@lesley.edu www.lesley.edu

Aaron M. Price

Editor, Social Studies Pearson 501 Boylston Street, Suite 900 Boston, MA 02116 Email:

aaron.m.price@pearson.com Phone: 617-671-2464

Lisa Sabatella

Project Manager CIGNA Healthcare 900 Cottage Grove Rd Bloomfield, CT 06002 Phone: 860-226-8717

Email:

LisaMarie.Sabatella@cigna.c

om

Clare J. Mazur

WebIT Release Management CIGNA Healthcare 900 Cottage Grove Rd Bloomfield, CT 06002 Phone: 860.226.0333

Email:

clare.mazur2@cigna.com

Melynda Peloquin

Project Manager United Healthgroup 450 Columbus Blvd Hartford, CT 06103 Email:

melynda_g_peloquin@uhc.c

om

Phone: 860-702-6954

Barbara Sorensen

Winds of Change magazine 4450 Arapahoe Ave. Ste 100 Boulder, CO 80303

Phone: (303) 448-8853 Email: woc@indra.com www.wocmag.org